Finding Aid of the Andrew Hamilton Papers LSC.1227
UCLA Library Special Collections
- U.S. Navy (Box 110, Box 111, Box 112, Box 113)
  - U.S.S. Los Angeles. (Box 112)
  - Wave research, Scripps. (Box 113)
  - Communiques. (Box 113)
- Communique - All the World Wonders. (Box 113)
- Miscellaneous - confidential. (Box 113)
- Public info, article material. (Box 113)
- Confidential. (Box 114)
- Speech material. (Box 114)
- Boy Scouts - Los Angeles council, magazine and book committee. (Box 114)
- Order of the golden bruin. (Box 114)
- Edison (Box 114, Box 115, Box 116)
  - Miscellaneous., (2 files) (Box 114)
  - Correspondence. (Box 115)
  - Extra chapters., (2 files) (Box 115)
  - Photos, duplicates. (Box 116)
  - The last chapter. (Box 116)
  - Books about. (Box 116)
- Abend, Hal. (Box 116)
- Baker. (Box 116)
- Banks. (Box 116)
- Coffey, Al. (Box 116)
- Harris. (Box 116)
- Harrison, Gil. (Box 116)
- Henshaw, Petty and Paul. (Box 116)
- Nishimuba. (Box 116)
- Tandy. (Box 117)
- Thompson. (Box 117)
- Turner. (Box 117)
- Wilkes. (Box 117)
- Agencies. (Box 117)
- The American Magazine. (Box 117)
- Liberty Magazine. (Box 117)
- Nation's Business. (Box 117)
- Personal. (Box 117)
- Popular Mechanics Magazine. (Box 117)
- Saturday Evening Post. (Box 117)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 117)
- Miscellaneous - correspondence. (Box 117)
- Letters recieved while overseas. (Box 118)
- Personal (have been answered). (Box 118)
- Log - Navy, July-December 1945. (Box 118)
- Letters from/to editors., (2 files) (Box 118)
- Food miscellaneous. (Box 119)
- Conservation prison camps., (2 files) (Box 119)
- Alcoholism in industry. (Box 120)
- Tomorrow's schools. (Box 120)
- Elks Magazine. (Box 121)
- Navy public relations. (Box 121)
- High school "Day in the Navy." (Box 121)
- Correspondence - Navy. (Box 121)
- Navy - PRC 11-2. (Box 122)
- Navy - Public relations manual. (Box 122)
- Your Navy. (Box 123)
- Electrical West. (Box 123)
- Toys for children. (Box 123)
- Miscellaneous unsold articles. (Box 123)
- Travel articles. (Box 123)
- Aniimal training. (Box 124)
- Ralph Cornell article. (Box 124)
- Personal correspondence. (Box 124)
- Automotive diagnostic repair centers. (Box 124)
- Chimps that read and write. (Box 124)
- Breastfeeding - Jeliffe materials. (Box 125)
- Diary of an extraordinary charter day. (Box 125)
- Medical diet service. (Box 125)
- Oberlite - Mr. Voevodsky. (Box 125)
- Lassie. (Box 125)
- Correspondence - Dick Stanton. (Box 126)
- The Queen Mary. (Box 126)
- UCLA on the Move. (Box 127)
- Miscellaneous magazine articles. (Box 127)
- Japanese Americans. (Box 127)
- Miscellaneous. (Box 127)
- Miscellaneous., (2 files) (Box 128)
- Westways NYT travel., (2 files) (Box 128, Box 129)
- Science Digest. (Box 129)
- Today's health and Executive Health. (Box 130)
- Reader's Digest., (2 files) (Box 130, Box 131)
- Transcript of a taped discussion in which AJH reminisces about his association with Admiral Chester W. Nimitz during World War II. (Box 131)
  (donated by Patty Carew, August 1976)
- Explorers, pre-1945-1960 (Box 131, Box 132)
  - pre-1945. (Box 131)
  - 1945-1950. (Box 131)
  - 1951-1955. (Box 131)
  - 1956-1960. (Box 132)
- V. Explorers. (Box 132)
- Elwood (Box 132)
  - Article writing. (Box 132)
  - Short story technique. (Box 132)